[Forging Justice]
[Episode 21]
Thirty tables?
Are you trying to get me
to retire early?
Dad, I'll pay for it myself.
You don't have to pay. It's fine.
Nonsense.
I am the court president.
Can you guarantee
that among all the guests,
no one wants a favor from me?
Can you guarantee every gift money
is above board?
Can you guarantee that people won't
gossip about this behind our backs?
Dad, a court president is also human.
You have to live your life.
We can't shut ourselves off
from all human connections.
But we can't apply it here,
you know?
Except for your classmates
and my colleagues,
no one else
is to be invited.
No red envelopes. Keep it low-key.
And also,
that buddy of yours, Li Xiang,
the one at the law firm,
he cannot come.
It would just look too suspicious.
Dad.
Are we handling a case?
Why are we practicing recusal?
I knew it.
You must be the one behind this,
telling him to make a fuss, right?
No, no.
Yes, it was me.
I told him to. So what?
Dad, you are the court president.
So for all these years,
you've kept saying no to this and that.
I endured it all.
I didn't say anything, did I?
But this is my wedding.
I'm only doing this once in my life.
Mom is gone,
and you're just brushing me off, right?
If we can't accept red envelopes
and can't invite people,
then what's the point of having a wedding?
Might as well just have
a New Year's Eve dinner.
We'll keep it simple.
Just two tables.
That's final.
Listen to your dad.
Be sensible.
Am I not sensible?
No, no.
It's not about you.
Alright, alright, calm down.
Why can't he be sentenced?
Doesn't he have to obey the law?
Do whatever he wants?
No, look.
He's a person with limited civil capacity.
He can't
be held accountable for his actions.
What kind of person?
I'll kill you!
A person with limited civil capacity...
Don't give me that nonsense.
I don't understand.
I can explain it to you.
It means
that when Yin Ping set fire
to your livestock shed,
he wasn't aware
of what he was doing.
Get it?
I don't get it!
I came to you because I respect the law.
You can't just sweep this under the rug!
If he doesn't know anything,
then how come when he saw her,
he yelled, "So white! So white!"?
Don't bring up things
unrelated to this case.
Then who will compensate for our loss?
Will you?
I think you should calm down first.
Fortunately, the livestock weren't hurt,
right?
Only the shed collapsed.
Let's go talk to the village committee.
Let's see if we can
come up with a solution.
What solution?
He's a menace!
He's going to cause a huge disaster
sooner or later!
So you can't do anything, right?
Fine.
Next time I'll take care of it myself.
Gun!
Gun! My gun!
Deal with him?
How?
Tell me, what am I supposed to do?
His parents died early.
It's just him and his grandma at home.
She can barely take care of herself,
let alone look after him.
Then can we send him
to a psychiatric hospital?
Who will pay for it?
The government should provide relief.
It won't cost much.
Well, no matter how much it costs,
someone has to pay for it.
My way's the cheapest.
I paid for it myself.
No.
Village Chief.
Ma'am.
Ping got into trouble again?
Just lie down and rest.
Sorry to bother you again.
No trouble at all.
Don't move!
Lihui.
Here.
Send these out separately
to the original trial court
and the original procuratorate.
Aren't we going to report
to the procuratorate first?
No need.
We'll send them in the names of
Prosecutor Guo Dajie and Zhang Lihui
from the Bieshan Prison.
Um...
Is this appropriate, Mentor?
It's fine.
What if
the procuratorate disagrees?
Then should we send these materials
or not?
Mentor.
I don't think your surname should be Guo.
It should be Jiang.
What? What Jiang?
''Jiang'' is always the spiciest!
Hey.
You...
Don't you think what I said makes sense?
You kid...
Guo.
It's enough that we received the appeal.
Anything extra
should be handled
by the original trial court.
If we interfere too much,
it will cause trouble
for the local authorities.
Yes, yes.
Well,
we have
studied this case file
carefully and repeatedly.
We believe
there is a real problem.
Discovering problems
and representing inmates
to seek legal relief
is also part of
our job responsibilities.
Right?
All right, just leave it here for now.
I have a meeting.
Comrade Lihui,
aren't you coming back yet?
We have several positions waiting for you
at the procuratorate.
Prosecutor You,
I'm tied up
with this case.
I'm waiting for you to cut me loose.
You taught her all this, didn't you?
Every line,
sharp as a tack.
Let's go.
Mentor,
did you see Prosecutor You's attitude?
Looks like we can only push this far.
[Linshan City People's Procuratorate]
How about we go to Nanlu?
Talk to them face to face
and force them to take it seriously.
Mentor,
if you have any concerns,
I'll go by myself.
What concerns would I have?
I'm about to retire.
What can they do to me?
I'm concerned about you.
You're disregarding leadership,
acting without authorization,
lacking perspective,
and asking for trouble.
Go buy the tickets.
How many?
How many should I buy?
What do you think?
Two tickets.
Two places, one heart.
After a 13-year journey of love,
our lawyer Lu Zeming
and Vice Principal Ding Rui
have finally tied the knot,
building a happy and blissful family.
This is the power of food!
This is the miracle of love!
What is the power of food?
Tell us more about it.
This is a romantic story.
We'll let the groom
tell you all about it later.
Let us
wish the newlyweds
a lifetime of happiness.
May they grow old together.
And to my former leader,
Court Pres. Ding Zhongxiang,
good health
and grandchildren soon!
Great!
Now let's have
the groom say a few words.
You go ahead, or should I?
Just say whatever.
Eat up, drink up!
Good!
We're all family here.
Great, great!
Let's hurry down.
Dad.
Dad, Mom.
Pour your parents a drink.
Come, come.
Here, Dad.
Well, let's just have a sip.
Dad.
Here, Dad.
Let me.
Alright. This is enough.
Come on, in-laws.
So happy.
Cheers.
I...
Where are you now?
I'm in Nanlu,
at the Municipal Procuratorate.
At the procuratorate?
That's great.
I really have to thank you guys.
If I hadn't met you,
I really
wouldn't have thought
of going for further studies.
No, that's all down to you.
Why didn't Zhang Lihui come?
Where is she now?
She's too far away.
She was transferred to Bieshan.
She's a prison resident prosecutor now.
Why did she go there?
Was it because
with her husband?
No.
She's always been single.
She was just transferred there.
Let's eat.
Come, come.
Court Pres. Ding.
Yizhong.
Congratulations.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
Have a seat.
Sit, sit.
Congratulations, Court Pres. Ding.
Yizhong.
It's been a long time.
It's been years.
You still look so energetic.
How have you been?
I'm good.
I'm so glad you could come.
How is Yingjie?
Is she feeling better?
What's wrong with her?
You don't know?
I don't know.
Okay, enjoy your meal.
A while back,
Fang Shumei
mentioned a few things to me.
That Xia,
she's always had a fiery temper.
We talked on the phone
a couple of days ago,
I thought she was doing research.
Young people, they keep things bottled up.
Plus, she is
quite competitive.
Yizhong,
when it comes to relationships,
sometimes it's about fate.
The one you can confide in
isn't always the one you end up with.
You're a grown man.
You need to be a bit more proactive.
How far have things gone
between the two of you?
There's
nothing going on between us.
Well,
why isn't presiding judge Fang here?
You don't want me to know?
Fine, I won't press you.
So that means
Xia didn't tell you
about Fang Shumei's situation
either, right?
I don't know.
Fang Shumei got divorced.
She's raising the child on her own,
so whenever there's a holiday,
she can't get away at all.
Court Pres. Ding,
congratulations.
Gaoyuan. Remember me?
Gaoyuan,
how could I not remember?
Congratulations. Congratulations to you.
You used to play basketball so well.
Tell me,
where are you working now?
Binjiang Intermediate People's Court.
You young people are truly impressive.
Let me introduce you.
This is Court Pres. Ding.
This is my wife, Fang Haohao.
Hello, Court Pres. Ding.
Hello.
Welcome to Nanyu.
Gaoyuan.
Let's be generous.
Slow down.
Let me say hello.
Gaoyuan!
Dad.
He is Deputy Court Pres. Yu now.
Look at him.
I knew you'd
value our friendship.
You'd definitely come.
Let me introduce. This is Ding Rui.
This is Zeming.
And this is my wife, Fang Haohao.
Say hello.
Hello, Mrs. Yu!
Hello, hello.
I've never met
his best buddy.
This time, I forced him to take time off.
We sat on a train for dozens of hours
just to come share the joy.
Thank you.
This...
A red envelope across thousands of miles,
the gift is generous,
and so is the friendship.
Take it.
Thank you, Mrs. Yu.
Alright, let's go enjoy the feast.
Let's go.
Let's go eat.
Well, Yu,
I need to talk to him for a second.
Alright.
You guys go ahead.
Mrs. Yu, come with us.
Alright, we'll go eat.
Let's go.
It's fine.
Congratulations.
Which table are we at?
What's wrong?
Xia Yingjie was sent down
to the countryside.
You agreed to it?
You know that, right?
You didn't even tell me.
No.
Why would I tell you this?
It's a big day today.
I'll talk to you about it another day.
No, wait.
On that case,
she was the only one
who advocated returning the file.
You know that, right?
Wasn't she wronged?
This matter is not that simple.
I shared the responsibility.
I was disciplined as well.
How were you disciplined?
You were promoted to Deputy Court Pres.
She was sent to a village.
The procuratorate wanted to commend her,
but comrade Xia Yingjie refused.
What could I do?
She's always been like this.
You know that.
Yu Gaoyuan, what is she like?
You are the Deputy Court Pres.
Couldn't you protect her in this matter?
One word from you,
and she wouldn't have ended up
in that village!
Hey, you're over thirty.
Why are you acting like a student?
She is a judge, an adult.
What kind of protection does she need?
She needs protection?
You, Chen Yizhong,
spend all your time in Beijing,
revising laws,
attending academic conferences,
surrounded by high-ranking and scholars.
Do you know what it's like
in the localities?
Yet you're here lecturing me.
You want to protect her? Go ahead.
Dashijia Village.
Buy a ticket tomorrow
and arrive the day after.
Go ahead.
Don't be mad at me. Let's go.
Let's go.
Fine, I'll go.
I'll go.
Mrs. Yu. Go easy on the drink.
I don't usually drink much.
Just a little bit.
Zeming,
are you trying to cause a scene?
Over there.
Dad, I didn't invite him.
How would I know his wife
would tag along?
Let me go say hi.
Come with me.
Qin.
Zeming.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mrs. Qin.
You look stunning.
Court Pres. Ding.
Congratulations.
Congratulations to you.
Thank you.
Court Pres. Ding, congratulations.
Court Pres. Ding.
Zhigao.
I appreciate the thought,
but I can't accept this.
Look.
How did they know?
This is just a small private dinner,
so I didn't notify everyone.
Please don't mind.
Of course not.
We know you
are very careful about public perception.
We understand.
Court Pres. Ding.
No.
Don't treat us as outsiders.
Gift money.
Zhigao,
you and Li Xiang make quite a team,
don't you?
We're mostly handling
small civil cases now.
We've got a decent reputation.
Good, good.
People from the county come specifically
looking for me.
That's great to see.
Court Pres. Ding,
we came today
firstly to congratulate you.
Secondly, there's a small matter.
Since you're in a good mood today,
we want to discuss it with you.
Mrs. Qin.
He's just too shy.
I had to drag him here.
Court Pres. Ding.
Let's talk another day.
-No.
-It's nothing.
Just a tiny favor.
One word from you is all it takes.
Alright, alright, fine.
Court Pres. Ding, please.
Just five minutes, okay?
Okay, five minutes.
Let's talk outside, okay?
Okay, thank you.
Thank you, Court Pres. Ding.
You guys go ahead.
You go on, go on.
Thank you.
I'm going out for a bit.
What do we do now?
Have a seat.
It's fine, Mrs. Yu.
They're making me sweat.
What? What is it?
Court Pres. Ding.
What's wrong?
Did you bully her?
No, I didn't.
What's wrong?
No, no, don't cry. What's wrong?
Court Pres. Ding,
do you still remember Xiaowen?
How could I forget?
Back then,
you stopped her from going to college,
and forced her to get married
in exchange for a 2,000-yuan bride price
to pay for Qin's medical bills.
But she was determined.
She left,
and cut off contact with you.
She's back now.
Just got back.
Then why
didn't she come with you?
She got divorced,
but she still holds a grudge against us.
She won't come home.
She's staying in Nanlu,
with her one-year-old child.
She hasn't made any money these years.
Life has been really tough
for her out there.
You two
should create conditions
to bring her back.
So you can all look out for each other.
Right?
That's exactly what we mean.
Court Pres. Ding,
I knew
you would help our Xiaowen.
I knew you would arrange
for Xiaowen to work in the court.
Thank you, Court Pres. Ding.
No, wait.
-Thank you.
-Court Pres. Ding.
Any work will do,
even odd jobs.
Right.
You've watched her grow up.
-Yes, yes.
-Wait.
She just hates him.
Wait.
And now she hates me too because of him.
That was his bad idea.
Listen to me!
Will you let me talk?
Please, go ahead.
Are you done?
Listen to me.
Hiring people requires a process.
I, alone,
can't make the decision.
Do you understand?
Yes.
We understand.
Court Pres. Ding,
we all know it's hard
to get things done now.
I understand this.
Well, you... you...
W-What are you doing?
No.
She doesn't know any better.
Please don't take it to heart.
Gift money, gift money.
Court Pres. Ding, it's clean money.
It's all the money I earned
from selling peanuts.
I believe the money
is honestly earned.
I only have this one daughter.
Please, have some mercy.
Let my daughter
have a peaceful
wedding today.
That's all I ask. Please.
I'm begging you.
Please, Court Pres. Ding.
Help Xiaowen.
I'm begging you, please.
Court Pres. Ding, I'll kneel down for you.
Pull your wife up.
Help your wife up.
What are you doing?
You are really a psycho!
Get up.
I beg you.
Get up, now!
Court Pres. Ding.
Get up! Stand up!
Gao Qiuyue, are you crazy?
Don't stop me!
Court Pres. Ding.
Court Pres. Ding, I'm begging you!
Stop it!
Court Pres. Ding!
Stop making a scene!
You've ruined everything!
You coward!
Oh, no.
Let's go home.
[1996, Nanlu City]
Check please!
Coming.
Kiddo,
remember this:
If they give us attitude,
we just pretend we don't see it.
This case of yours,
the first trial sent it back twice.
Then there were two more appeals.
Who knows how many
people have handled it by now.
If it's a wrongful conviction,
all these people will be held accountable
in the future.
Think about the pushback we'll get.
But the longer it drags on,
the worse the liability gets, right?
That's true enough.
Mentor, do you mean
they know it's a wrongful conviction,
but to protect themselves,
they won't admit it?
Just from the case file,
we found so many problems.
This case went through two trials,
passed through so many hands,
and not one person noticed?
Is that possible?
Impossible.
I don't understand either.
If it were me,
if I found a problem with a case,
I would definitely
bring it up immediately.
But not necessarily.
Five or six years ago,
I wouldn't have.
Look at you.
Prison
can really reform people.
It's you who reforms people, Mentor.
Me?
A case
passes through countless hands,
and invisibly,
the responsibility gets diluted.
Everyone thinks:
I'm only responsible
for my little piece of it.
Or,
I'm only responsible to my superior.
As for what the case
is really about,
that's not for me to decide.
So now,
how do we fix this?
Haven't they been talking about
judicial reform?
This is exactly what needs to change.
We need to fix it at the root.
How's the food, you two?
Great, it's great.
Sir.
My classmates and I
used to come to Nanlu a lot.
The first thing we did
after getting off the bus
was to come here for noodles.
You always gave us extra meat.
I'm sorry.
I'll get you some more meat right away.
Welcome back to Nanlu, old friend.
No, Sir.
That's not what I meant.
Don't be afraid.
He's a gentle lunatic.
He doesn't hurt people.
Don't move!
Ropes. I'm afraid of ropes.
Afraid of ropes.
Hit, hit, hit!
Your grandma will bring you food tonight.
So you just keep him chained up like this?
Just poop right here.
What? Should I cuddle him?
It's resolved.
Is that how it's resolved?
He's a human, not an animal!
You're from the big city.
You don't understand.
Go, go, go.
Hurry, hurry, hurry. Go.
This is how it is in the countryside.
There's only so much I can do.
Excuse me.
No!
[Nanlu City People's Procuratorate]
We have received the materials
and studied them.
This case caused quite a stir
in Nanlu back then.
After all, the criminal's methods
were too cruel.
Later, Yan Jicai recanted
his confession in court.
It was full of twists and turns.
There was immense pressure from all sides.
You weren't there,
so it's hard to understand
that kind of pressure.
Everyone works very hard.
You can't just
come here and hassle us
because a criminal is being difficult.
Lin,
take this to Chen.
Yes,
you're right.
He is
just stubborn.
He recanted with us too,
saying it wasn't him.
He banged his head against the wall,
getting blood everywhere.
What we
really mean is,
we want to get to
the bottom of this case.
You need to make him give up.
So he stops banging his head all the time,
or attempting suicide.
If you think
there's a problem with this case,
I can answer your questions.
But to get a retrial,
without new evidence,
it's basically impossible.
Basically impossible.
We worked so hard all day
just for him to say this?
We still learned something.
At least we know
where they stand now.
I don't think they'll take it seriously
without official backing.
Let's go.
Hello?
Prosecutor You.
Guo,
aren't you on vacation?
Why did you go to Nanlu?
This case,
I really can't let it go.
Guo Dajie,
do you have any sense
of organizational discipline?
Prosecutor You.
I'm a bit obsessed now.
This case is haunting me.
My... my mental state
is... a little off.
You know?
If you don't figure it out,
I'll die
with my eyes open.
Cut the crap.
You seem perfectly normal to me.
Prosecutor You.
We've known each other for so many years.
I've never...
You've never asked me for anything.
Is that what you want to say?
That's what I call true buddies.
I've never asked you for anything either.
Now,
I'm begging you,
stop causing trouble
for the procuratorate.
Come back immediately.
Hello?
The line is crackling.
I can't hear you clearly.
Well, Prosecutor You,
just listen to me.
I'm not asking for much.
Just have our procuratorate
send a fax over here,
requesting them
to allow us to review
all the case files from that year.
That's all.
Us?
Who else went besides you?
I...
Hello?
This phone line is terrible.
Can't hear a thing.
Guo,
this isn't like you.
You're being so reckless.
Think about it.
What if we dig everything up
and find nothing wrong?
How are we going to
explain ourselves to our Nanlu comrades?
I can hear you now.
Prosecutor You.
Statistically speaking,
what do you think
the odds are that there's never been
a wrongful conviction?
On my honor as a prosecutor,
I guarantee you
that this case
definitely has a problem!
Since we've already started,
I'm determined to get to the bottom
of this case!
Prosecutor You,
are you still there?
Prosecutor You.
Listen to me, Guo.
This is the last time!
How did it go?
The fax will be here today.
You're the best, Mentor.
Lihui?
Zheng Jianmin.
It really is you.
Don't be scared.
It's okay.
Food.
I want...
I want my mom.
Here.
Grandma is sleeping.
Food.
Delicious food.
Let me pour you some.
Go on, eat.
Good, good.
Why are you here?
Came to see you.
Murder!
You two experts,
what are your thoughts?
You're being modest.
Your archives
are organized
far better than ours.
We've gained a lot.
Prosecutor Wang,
we'd like to ask you about a few details.
Go ahead.
In Lin Yan's
eight fingernails,
human tissue was found.
But in the case file,
there's no
DNA evaluation report.
Back then, we asked the police
to conduct a supplementary investigation.
Their reply was
that it was unrelated to the case.
So it wasn't included in the file.
Unrelated?
Meaning
among the known associates,
there was no DNA match?
Yes.
Doesn't that prove
the suspect is a stranger?
Young lady,
you can't rely entirely on deduction
to handle a case.
She's no ordinary young lady.
She graduated from a top university,
and got her Ph.D. while working
under Zhou Yipu.
That's
very authoritative.
Yan Jicai
said he left the victim
on Shengli Street.
By then, it was already
past midnight.
A young woman
standing on the street is very noticeable.
Were there no witnesses?
No.
We did the math.
According to the indictment,
Yan Jicai actually didn't have
enough time to commit the crime.
But according to what Yan Jicai said,
the timeline checks out.
Dr. Zhang.
Just call me Zhang, please.
How long have you been a prosecutor?
Twelve years.
We should all know that
once an event has occurred,
it's impossible
to reconstruct it 100%.
You'd agree with that, right?
But I think
factual reconstruction
and logical consistency
are two different things.
Zhang,
do you know
what the easiest thing in this world is?
Finding faults.
Wang.
Don't get us wrong.
That's not why we're here.
His methods were so brutal,
and he only got a death sentence
with a reprieve.
That already takes into full account
the specifics of this case.
And by specifics, you mean
the chain of evidence
isn't complete enough, right?
The facts are basically clear.
The evidence is basically conclusive.
These two basics,
I think
we've met both.
I think you are wrong.
Wrong?
Wrong.
The "two basics" are a nationally issued
guiding principle for adjudication.
How dare you say they are wrong?
Now, Lihui, Lihui.
Calm down, calm down.
Wang.
Come, sit down.
Let's all calm down.
"Basic facts are clear"
and "basic evidence is conclusive"
are not the same thing as
"the facts are basically clear"
and "the evidence is
basically conclusive."
Dr. Zhang,
you are very good at splitting hairs.
This is not a word game.
In this case,
we failed to figure out the basic facts
and basic evidence.
Okay.
Then please figure it out, you two.
Once you figure it out, we'll restart
and review it.
Wang.
Kiddo,
someone is treating you to dinner tonight.
Zheng Jianmin.
Waiting for us?
How long have you been waiting?
I didn't check the time.
I want to treat you to dinner.
You go ahead.
What about you?
I have things to do.
Make him pay.
Let's go together.
I'm not going. I'm busy.
Judge Xia,
why did you release Yin Ping?
I felt so sorry for him.
I... I did untie the chains
from his feet,
but I still bolted
the door.
That door's rotten.
A bolt wouldn't hold it.
Do you think I'm making excuses
for myself?
I'm sorry.
Yin Ping,
even if he does have mental issues,
he's still a human being.
Kept like a dog
on a chain.
He ate, slept, relieved himself
all in that room.
He didn't even have a quilt.
It was too miserable.
By the way,
were you involved earlier
in mediating the case
between Hu Xudong and Yin Ping?
Yes.
Yin Ping set fire to Hu Xudong's
livestock shed.
I heard Hu Xudong
was very dissatisfied with the mediation.
Because Yin Ping
was unable to compensate for the losses.
All right.
That's it for now.
Thank you, Judge Xia.
I might come to see you again.
Comrade.
Did I make
a very serious mistake last night?
Let's go.
They're out.
Sorry for the trouble.
We're leaving now.
Thanks for your hard work.
What does that mean?
We're leaving.
Officer, any clues yet?
She is the one
who let Yin Ping out.
You're getting people killed!
You're from the city.
You don't know how hard it is
for country folks.
Isn't that just hypocritical sympathy?
Right, putting on an act!
Nothing but an act!
Enough, enough! What do you know?
-Go home!
-Just putting on airs!
Get out of here!
In my opinion,
the real culprit is that...
Stop it.
-Go home.
-Just putting on airs!
Out! Out!
Are you okay?
It's their house.
When
are you going back?
Let's go.
You didn't call your mentor,
and snuck out on your own
for a good meal?
He's still sleeping.
Should I wake him up?
No, I'm just kidding.
Let Mr. Guo get some good rest.
Is it far?
We've got a ride.
I'm telling you, that rice noodle place
is amazing.
There's a line every morning.
You'll definitely love it.
Okay.
It's a deal then.
You treated me yesterday,
today's on me.
Okay.
You said yesterday
that your second round of training
was at my school.
Then how come we never met?
We did.
At your master's graduation ceremony,
I was watching from the audience.
Then why didn't you come up
and say hi to me?
I didn't think I was good enough.
I was too embarrassed.
What goes on in your head?
I don't think that way anymore.
The ride.
Let's go.
Here, enjoy your meal.
It smells pretty good.
When I said I wanted to be a judge,
none of you
took it seriously.
Only you actually gave me books
and notes to read.
If it weren't for you,
I might still be at the Nanyu Court,
fixing windows and doors.
I really didn't think that much about it.
I grew up relying on
other people's kindness.
People helped me,
so I naturally help others.
You said you wanted
to advance professionally,
so I thought
you needed that kind of help.
I thought it was because
we just really hit it off.
We still hit it off now.
Otherwise, why would I have
had two meals in a row with you?
My mentor is going to eat noodles
alone again today.
That's true.
To be honest,
are we a nuisance
to you guys?
If it weren't for the fax
from your procuratorate,
probably no one would bother with you.
Right now, the best you can hope for
is reluctant cooperation.
Your request landed on
our prosecution division.
I didn't handle that case.
But the colleagues who did
are all pretty resistant.
You should be prepared for that.
The cold shoulders have already started.
Can you do me a favor?
Could you get that DNA test report
so we can take a look at it?
It's not in the file.
No wonder you treated me to dinner today.
I'm kidding.
I'm not kidding.
It's likely the police
never even forwarded it
to our procuratorate.
It might still be in their
supplementary investigation files.
But honestly,
just based on the DNA
found in the fingernails
not matching Yan Jicai,
it will hardly be enough
to overturn the verdict.
You are a prosecutor now.
Don't you see gaping holes
in this conviction logic?
Yan Jicai should be acquitted.
Am I wrong?
If I were a judge,
I might acquit him.
But I'm a prosecutor.
My job is to fight crime.